http://www.arcstreamav.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyArcStream AV, Inc. (“ArcStream AV,” “ABBREVIATION,” “we,” “us,” “our,” or the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company’s Websites (“Visitors”), individuals who register to use the Services as defined below (“Customers”), and individuals who register to attend the Company’s corporate events (“Attendees”). This Privacy Statement describes ArcStream AV’s privacy practices in relation to the use of the Company’s Websites and the related applications, services, and programs offered by ArcStream AV (collectively, the “Services”), as well as individuals’ choices regarding use, access and correction of personal information. If you have questions or complaints regarding ArcStream AV’s Privacy Statement or associated practices, please contact us here. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact us at john@ArcStream AV. 1. Services coveredThis Privacy Statement covers the information practices, including how the Company collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, of Websites that link to this Privacy Statement (collectively referred to as “ArcStream AV’s Websites” or “the Company’s Websites”).ArcStream AV’s Websites may contain links to other Websites. The information practices or the content of such other Websites is governed by the privacy statements of such other Websites. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of other Websites to understand their information practices. 2. InformationWhen expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services, or registering to use the Websites or other Services, or registering for an event, ArcStream AV requires you to provide the Company with personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address (“Required Contact Information”). When purchasing the Services or registering for an appointment, ArcStream AV may also require you to provide the Company with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Services (“Billing Information”). ArcStream AV may also ask you to provide additional information, such as company annual revenues, number of employees, or industry (“Optional Information”). When Visitors apply for a job with the Company, ArcStream AV may also require you to submit additional personal information as well as a resume or curriculum vitae (“Applicant Information”). We also may store as part of our service details on your customers including special catagoeries of data. We retain this information in line with our retention policy which is available on request.Required Contact Information, Billing Information, Applicant Information, Optional Information and any other information you submit to ArcStream AV to or through the Services are referred to collectively as “Data.” As you navigate the Company’s Websites, ArcStream AV may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons (“Web Site Navigational Information”). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Company’s Websites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked). Through our “import contacts” feature option, we may also collect information such as the name, company name, address, phone number or email address of contacts that you choose to share with us.  When you provide us with personal information about your contacts, we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided, such as to add new records to your ArcStream AV account. 3. Use of information collectedThe Company uses Data about ArcStream AV Customers to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” Web form, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Services. The Company also uses Data about ArcStream AV Attendees to plan and host corporate events, host online forums and social networks in which event Attendees may participate, and to populate online profiles for Attendees on the Company’s Websites. Additional information on the Company’s privacy practices with respect to Data about ArcStream AV Attendees may be found in additional privacy statements on the event Websites, as the case may be. Please see here for more information on bulletin boards, blogs or chat rooms provided by ArcStream AV in connection with its corporate events. The Company may also use Data about ArcStream AV Customers and Attendees for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use the information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company, its affiliates, and its partners, such as information about promotions or events. ArcStream AV may also receive information about Customers and Attendees from other sources, including third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this information with Data we already have about you.  This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and create more tailored advertising to provide products and services that may be of interest to you. ArcStream AV uses Web Site Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s Websites. The Company may also use Web Site Navigational Information alone or in combination with Data about ArcStream AV Customers and Data about ArcStream AV Attendees to provide personalized information about the Company. ArcStream AV partners with third parties to display advertising on our Websites and Services or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use cookies or similar technologies provide you advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click here, or if located in the European Union please contact us. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 4. Web Site Navigational InformationCookies, Web Beacons and IP AddressesArcStream AV uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the Company’s Websites (“Web Site Navigational Information”). As described more fully below, we and our partners use these cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer Websites and Services, track users’ movements around our Websites and Services, serve targeted advertisements and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  This section describes the types of Web Site Navigational Information used on the Company’s Websites and Services, and how this information may be used. CookiesArcStream AV uses cookies to make interactions with the Company’s Websites easy and meaningful. When you visit one of the Company’s Websites, ArcStream AV’s servers send a cookie to your computer or device. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you; they merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to ArcStream AV, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a Web form (such as a “Contact Me” or a “Free Trial” Web form) or have previously identified yourself to ArcStream AV, you remain anonymous to the Company. ArcStream AV uses cookies that are session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer or device when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer or device after you close your browser or turn off your computer. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our Websites or Services. The following sets out how ArcStream AV uses different categories of cookies and your options for managing cookies’ settings: Required CookiesRequired cookies enable you to navigate the Company’s Websites and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Websites and using ArcStream AV Services.Managing SettingsBecause required cookies are essential to operating the Company’s Websites and the Services, there is no option to opt out of these cookies.Functionality cookiesFunctionality cookies allow the Company’s Websites and Services to remember information you have entered or choices you make (such as your username, language, or your region) and provide enhanced, more personal features.  These cookies also enable you to optimize your use of ArcStream AV’s Websites and Services after logging in. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. Managing SettingsTo manage the use of functionality cookies on this Website, or to opt out of their use, click "Cookie Preferences" in the footer of this page. Note that opting out may impact the functionality you receive when using ArcStream AV's Websites and Services. To learn more about how to control cookies using your browser settings click here. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here.  Log Files, IP Addresses, URLs and Other DataAs is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer our Websites and Services.  This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), device and application identification numbers, your location, your browser type, your Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, the pages and files you viewed, your searches, your operating system and system configuration information, and date/time stamps associated with your usage. Due to Internet communications standards, when you visit or use the Company’s Web sites and Services, we automatically receive the URL of the website from which you came and the website to which you go when you leave our Website. This information is used to analyze overall trends, to help us improve our Websites and Services, to track and aggregate non-personal information, and to provide the Websites and Services. For example, ArcStream AV uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company’s Websites. ArcStream AV also collects IP addresses from Customers when they log into the Services as part of the Company’s “Identity Confirmation” and “IP Range Restrictions” security features. Social Media Features and Single Sign-onThe Company’s Websites may use social media features, such as the Facebook “like” button (“Social Media Features”). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Company’s Web site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on the Company’s Web site to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party social media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Company’s Web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features. ArcStream AV also allows you to log in to certain of our Websites and Services using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you with the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign-up form. Do Not TrackCurrently, various browsers — including Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari — offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to Websites’ visited by the user about the user's browser DNT preference setting. ArcStream AV does not currently commit to responding to browsers' DNT signals with respect to the Company's Websites, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent. ArcStream AV takes privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard. 5. Public forums, refer a contact, and customer testimonialsArcStream AV may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on the Company’s Websites. Any personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. ArcStream AV is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. Customers and Visitors may elect to use the Company’s referral program to inform contacts about the Company’s Websites and Services. When using the referral program, the Company requests the contact’s name and email address. ArcStream AV will automatically send the contact a one–time email inviting him or her to visit the Company’s Websites. ArcStream AV does not store this information. ArcStream AV posts a list of Customers and testimonials on the Company’s Websites that contain information such as Customer names and titles. ArcStream AV obtains the consent of each Customer prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials. 6. Sharing of information collectedService ProvidersArcStream AV may share Data about ArcStream AV Visitors, Customers and Attendees with the Company’s contracted service providers so that these service providers can provide services on our behalf. These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide the requested services to us.  Without limiting the foregoing, ArcStream AV may also share Data about ArcStream AV Visitors, Customers and Attendees with the Company’s service providers to ensure the quality of information provided, and with third-party social networking and media Websites, such as Facebook, for marketing and advertising on those Websites. Unless described in this Privacy Statement, ArcStream AV does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes. ArcStream AV AffiliatesThe Company may share Data about ArcStream AV Customers with other companies in order to work with them, including affiliates of the ArcStream AV corporate group. For example, the Company may need to share Data about ArcStream AV Customers with other companies within the ArcStream AV corporate family for customer support, marketing, technical operations and account management purposes. Business PartnersFrom time to time, ArcStream AV may partner with other companies to jointly offer products,  services, or programs (such as webinars or downloadable content). If you purchase, specifically express interest in, or register for a jointly–offered product, service, or program from or through ArcStream AV, the Company may share Data about ArcStream AV Customers collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our partner(s). ArcStream AV does not control our business partners’ use of the Data about ArcStream AV Customers that we collect, and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly-offered product or service. ArcStream AV does not share Data about ArcStream AV Attendees with business partners unless: (1) you specifically opt-in to such sharing via an event registration form; or (2) you attend a Company event and allow ArcStream AV or any of its business partners to scan your attendee badge. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to opt-in via event registration forms and elect not to have your badge scanned at Company events.  If you choose to share your information with business partners in the manners described above, your information will be subject to the business partners’ respective privacy statements. Third PartiesSection 4 of this Privacy Statement, Web Site Navigational Information, specifically addresses the information we or third parties collect through cookies and web beacons, and how you can control cookies through your Web browsers.  We may also disclose your personal information to any third party with your prior consent. BillingArcStream AV uses a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company’s behalf. Compelled DisclosureArcStream AV reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if the Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. 7. International transfer of information collectedThe Company primarily stores Data about ArcStream AV Customers and Data about ArcStream AV Attendees in the United States. To facilitate ArcStream AV’s global operations, the Company may transfer and access such information from around the world, including from other countries in which the Company has operations. This Privacy Statement shall apply even if ArcStream AV transfers Data about ArcStream AV Customers or Data about ArcStream AV Attendees to other countries.8. Communications preferencesArcStream AV offers Visitors, Customers, and Attendees who provide contact information a means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of the Company’s marketing emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe by contacting us using the information in the “Contacting Us" section below.9. Correcting and updating your informationArcStream AV may retain your information for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection. For instance, we may retain your information during the time in which you have an account to use our Websites or Services and for a reasonable period of time afterwards. We also may retain your information during the period of time needed for ArcStream AV to pursue our legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. You may request to review, correct, delete or otherwise modify any of the personal information that you have previously provided to us through the Company’s Websites and Services.  If you have registered for an account with ArcStream AV, you may generally update your user settings, profile, organization’s settings or event registration by contacting us. To update your billing information, discontinue your account, and/or request return or deletion of Your Data associated with your account, please contact us. For other requests to access, correct, modify or delete Your Data, please review the “Contacting Us” section below.  Requests to access, change, or delete your information will be addressed within a reasonable timeframe. 10. Customer DataArcStream AV’s Customers may electronically submit data or information to the Services for hosting and processing purposes (“Customer Data”). ArcStream AV will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except when required by law. ArcStream AV only access Customer Data only for the purpose of providing the Services or preventing or addressing service or technical problems or as may be required by law. ArcStream AV acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information.  If personal information pertaining to you as an individual has been submitted to us by an ArcStream AV customer and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, amend, or delete such data, please inquire with our customer directly. Because ArcStream AV personnel have limited ability to access data our customers submit to our Services, if you wish to make your request directly to ArcStream AV, please provide the name of the ArcStream AV customer who submitted your data to our Services.  We will refer your request to that customer, and will support them as needed in responding to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 11. SecurityArcStream AV uses appropriate technical and organisational security measures to protect Data about ArcStream AV Customers. 12. Changes to this Privacy StatementArcStream AV reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. 14. Contacting usQuestions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of the Company’s Websites and Services should be directed to ArcStream AV Privacy by completing our Contact Form or by mailing us at:ArcStream AV Limitedinfo@arcstreamav.comUNIT 4, FIRST QUARTER, BLENHEIM ROAD, EPSOM, KT19 9QN
View the latest Arcstream AV projects...
Interactive display wall is a winner at the Quilter Internationals
Adecco recruits Arcstream to create coordinated interactive AV experience
When you design for Cartier, diamonds are forever!
